kamalaharris.org 2008-05-11

# Privacy Policy | Kamala Harris

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
KamalaHarris.org is committed to protecting your privacy. While using our website, you do not have to identify yourself or disclose any personal information. Any personal information that is collected, is used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Statement. 

**Personal Information We May Collect**  
When you sign up on KamalaHarris.org, we may ask for your name, address, telephone number, email address, and other information. We use the information you provide to send you the latest news and updates from Kamala Harris. We do not share this information with any other candidates, parties or organizations, although we may send you information regarding political events, candidates and organizations at their request. 

When you agree to be listed as a “public endorser,” you agree that we may use your name in advertisements, press releases, and other public communications.

When you contribute money online: under San Francisco and California campaign laws, we are required to make periodic filings that provide the San Francisco Ethics Commission and other governmental entities with information on each contributor: name, address, amount of contribution, date of contribution, employer and occupation. To make a contribution online, we also ask for your credit card number and its expiration date.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**  
KamalaHarris.org collects and uses your personal information to deliver communications to you. We may also use these information in the course of regular campaign activities, such as reminding voters to vote on Election Day.  

Any vendors who may be hired to facilitate these communications are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Control of your Personal Information**  
To unsubscribe via email, send a message to [volunteer@kamalaharris.org](mailto:volunteer@kamalaharris.org). To contact us via email for general questions or comments, visit <http://www.kamalaharris.org/contact>. To contact us or unsubscribe via US Mail: Send a letter with your full name and email address to: Re-elect District Attorney Kamala Harris,  P.O. Box 78393, San Francisco, CA 94107-8393.

**Collection and Use of Children's Personal Information**  
We care about the safety and privacy of children online, and we comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). COPPA and its accompanying FTC regulations establish United States federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. Our site is not intended to solicit information of any kind from children under 13. 

**How do we protect your information?**  
Our website has a number of security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. Computer systems have restricted access limited only to those persons and organizations necessary to the proper functioning of KamalaHarris.Org. This access applies to all electronic and physical security measures. Highly sensitive data including credit card information is additionally secured through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**IP Addresses and Log File Data**  
We log IP address, which is the location of your computer or network on the Internet, for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. We also use page hits in the aggregate to track the popularity of pages that people visit in order to improve the quality of the site. There is no personal identifiable information collected in our log files.  
**  
Enforcement of this Privacy Statement**  
If you have questions regarding this statement, contact KamalaHarris.org via e-mail at [volunteer@kamalaharris.org](mailto:volunteer@kamalaharris.org) or by mail to Re-elect District Attorney Kamala Harris,  P.O. Box 78393, San Francisco, CA 94107-8393.

**Contact Information**  
KamalaHarris.org welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that KamalaHarris.org has not adhered to this Statement, please contact us by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail.

Re-elect District Attorney Kamala Harris  
P.O. Box 78393  
San Francisco, CA 94107-8393
